college24by7.com 2015-06-12

# online college management|admission, attendance, academics management, online classes, results & notifications

Privacy Policy..

      [College24by7.com](http://www.college24by7.com/ "College24by7") respects your individual privacy. This Privacy Policy ('Policy') embodies our commitment to its protection through adherence to fair electronic information practices. This Policy puts you, the individual, in control of how your personal information is processed. You have our promise that we will not electronically process your personal information in any way that is incompatible with this Policy.

Assurance

      [College24by7.com](http://www.college24by7.com/ "College24by7") assures you that we take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. We also implement reasonable policies and procedures to ensure that personal information is kept only for the purposes for which it has been gathered. 

|   
---|---  
  
            We take reasonable measures to ensure that we have accurately and completely recorded the personal information you have provided and also we provide reasonable access to your personal information as well as procedures for correcting or modifying that information where appropriate. We ensure accountability to individuals who believe that www.college24by7.com has not complied with these privacy principles.

How we put information to good use

      We use information about you for purposes of monitoring and improving our internal operations, as well as to ensure we administer your account in accordance with your agreements with us, and properly perform the services you have requested. Use of information is for cookie files to make it easier for users to access our site or services. A cookie file is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. However, the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie.

      You may refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. Finally, we use the information we collect to direct important notices and information affecting your account or services, as well as to provide general information that may be of interest to you, including information about our service or product offerings or the offerings of our business affiliates, changes in services or term conditions. You may unsubscribe of receiving information from us simply by notifying us of your desire in accordance with not to receive any information message from us. Note, however, that in order to fulfill our service obligations to you, we must continue sending you notices and other important information affecting your account or services

User Accountability

      Only those [college24by7.com](http://www.college24by7.com/ "College24by7") members that have a lawful purpose for accessing and handling personal information obtained by us are given authorization to do so. The unauthorized access or use of such information by a www.college24by7.com employee is prohibited and constitutes grounds for disciplinary action. Additionally, our information management systems are configured in such a way as to block or hold back employees from accessing information that they have no authority to access. If you feel that www.college24by7.com, or any of our agents, representatives or employees, is violating this Privacy Policy, please contact us: Via e-mail at: **info@college24by7.com** ,By telephone at: **(040) 3040-1234**
